var questions = [{
	"question": "What is the capital city of Nepal ? ?",
	"option1": "Lalitpur",
	"option2": "Bhaktapur",
	"option3": "Kathmandu",
	"option4": "Pokhara",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "The first mechsnicsl computer design by charles babbage was called ?",
	"option1": "Abacus",
	"option2": "Analytical Engine",
	"option3": "Calculator",
	"option4": "Processor",
	"answer": "2"
}, {
	"question": "Whic one is the first search engine in internet.",
	"option1": "Google",
	"option2": "Archie",
	"option3": "Altavista",
	"option4": "Bing",
	"answer": "2"
}, {
	"question": "Whic of the following is not a Database management software.",
	"option1": "MySQL",
	"option2": "Oracle",
	"option3": "Sybase",
	"option4": "COBOL",
	"answer": "4"
}, {
	"question": ".gif is an extension of.",
	"option1": "Image File",
	"option2": "Video File",
	"option3": "Audio File",
	"option4": "Word File",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "Number of bit used by the IPv6 address.",
	"option1": "32 bit",
	"option2": "64 bit",
	"option3": "128 bit",
	"option4": "256 bit",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "Firewall in computer is used for.",
	"option1": "Security",
	"option2": "Data Transmission",
	"option3": "Authentication",
	"option4": "Monitoring",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "The Number of layer in OSI model.",
	"option1": "4",
	"option2": "8",
	"option3": "7",
	"option4": "6",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "Where is the headquter of Microsoft office located.",
	"option1": "Texas",
	"option2": "New York",
	"option3": "California",
	"option4": "Washington",
	"answer": "4"
}, {
	"question": "Whic protocol is used to send E-mail.",
	"option1": "HTTP",
	"option2": "POP3",
	"option3": "SMTP",
	"option4": "SSH",
	"answer": "3"
}];
